Why It is because
we like to what
happened during Reaganomics And
we think Trumponomics resembles
greatly actually Reaganomics
And look what happened
to the dollar back
then Now it was
coming from the of
in the late 70s
But it really went
into overdrive to the
point where all the
treasury and ministers around
the got together and
said this is becoming
a deflationary risk to
the rest of the
because a lot of
debt is
denominated was and still
is denominated in
dollars So the debt
service was getting more
and expensive back then
We think we're not
going to see a
like we did in
the early 80s But
we think the pressure
is to the upside
if you look at
this chart in the
context of you will
see that we are
closer if you take
out that boom in
the early 80s we're
closer to the higher
end of the
dollar's than
we are to the
end And again I
think that goes against
conventional thinking right
now